paulfrasercollectibles.com 2019-07-31

# Privacy policy | Paul Fraser Collectibles

**Privacy Policy** ** **

**_"Just Collecting Ltd"_** **   **

**Trading as Paul Fraser Collectibles  ** ** _www.paulfrasercollectibles.com_**

 At Paul Fraser Collectibles we recognise that privacy and security is a major priority. 

Here we set out how we use and protect your personal information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and check back periodically for updates. 

**Our Privacy Commitment**  

The PaulFraserCollectibles.com website(s) is owned and operated by Just Collecting Limited. We are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. We will only collect, store and use your personal information for specific purposes. We use your personal information to support and enhance our relationship with you. We only share your personal information in accordance with the **General Data Protection Regulation**   **2018** **(GDPR)** **,** the **Data Protection Act 1998 (DPA)** and other applicable laws. You may contact Paul Fraser Collectibles at any time with any privacy questions or concerns, and to request access to the personal information we hold about you. You can also contact us with any corrections to this data or deletion requests. 

**Consent**  

Your use of the PaulFraserCollectibles.com website(s) and any disclosure of personal information via the website signifies your consent to us collecting and using personal information about you in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**Information about you**  

When a customer or designer (this is what we call our marketplace sellers) register with Paul Fraser Collectibles we ask for information and keep a record of such information, including; 

  * Name
  * E-mail address
  * Postal address
  * Phone number
  * Order history

All this is necessary so we can recognise you as a registered subscriber and customer, administer details of your order(s), and ensure that you are happy with the service you receive. We keep a record of any purchase you make from the Paul Fraser Collectibles store. This means we can help to deal quickly with any queries or problems you may have, and also so we can ensure that any information that we send you is relevant. 

We keep a record of all e-mail correspondence you send us, so we can track any problems or concerns you've had with any of the partners' stores on our website. 

We'll also ask you questions at registration, and from time to time by email, that will give us information that will be used to improve your experience of using and shopping at Paul Fraser Collectibles. You do not have to answer these questions, but if you do we can communicate with you in a more relevant way. 

If you would like to revise the information you have provided to us, or feel that what we currently have on record is incorrect, you may update the information by contacting us. 

**How we use your personal data**  

All the information we collect via our website or through correspondence with you is used to operate and improve the service we offer you and to personalise our service. We are committed to using your personal information only for: 

  * The supply of goods and services to you and for customer administration.
  * Planning and managing Paul Fraser Collectibles business activities, including analysis of customers' shopping habits, product and style preferences to improve our service.
  * Technical administration of our website.
  * Providing you with information about the services we offer.
  * Letting you know about offers and news from Paul Fraser Collectibles.
  * Letting you know about offers, news and products from partner stores on our site.
  * Passing your details to the designated courier in order to fulfil delivery of your order.
  * To verify details of your payment method or credit card account. 

Occasionally we will let you know about offers from other companies who we believe may interest you, either by sending out the information ourselves to you directly, or by providing certain details to other companies so they may contact you directly. 

We do not store credit card details nor do we share financial details with any 3rd parties. 

**Circumstances in which we may share some of your data with others:**  

In the unlikely event that our business assets are ever sold to or purchased by another company (our data records are part of our business). You will receive notice of any such event and we will use our reasonable endeavours to ensure that the new combined entity will follow the practices disclosed in this Privacy Policy. 

To outside research companies whom we may ask to contact you directly for your opinions on our service. In which case we provide them with only the information they need to perform their function. 

We occasionally make names, addresses and email addresses available to companies whose products we think may interest you, unless you have subsequently withdrawn that permission. 

If we are requested by the police or a regulatory or government authority investigating illegal activities to provide information concerning your activities whilst using Paul Fraser Collectibles we shall do so. 

**Cookies**  

A cookie is a small text file that a website can send to your computer's browser. It's like an internet user's identification card, which tells a website when a user is re-visiting the site. Their ability is limited to containing and transferring to the website as much information as the users have disclosed to that site. Cookies can't read or interfere with other information saved on your hard drive. The Paul Fraser Collectibles website (in common with most other shopping websites) will not work without cookies. 

Most computers are set up to automatically accept cookies. However, you can reset your browser settings to refuse cookies, or alert you when a cookie is being sent so you can choose whether or not to accept it. 

**Data over the internet**  

The internet is a global network, so it is possible for your data to travel internationally, which may include places both inside and outside the European Union. If you visit or shop at Paul Fraser Collectibles, you're agreeing and authorising us to process data in this way. 

**How we protect information** ** **

We take every precaution to protect your information. 

To this end all personal information stored by us is kept on a server in a secure environment. Only employees and any sub-contractors who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. 

You acknowledge that the internet is not a 100% secure medium for communication and, accordingly, we cannot fully guarantee the security of any information you send to us (or we send to you) via the internet. We are not responsible for any damages which you, or others, may suffer as a result of the loss of confidentiality of such information. 

**How you can help us protect your information**  

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online in non-protected environments - for example on message boards, through email, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Also remember to close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or internet café. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. 

**Further information**  

If you have questions about your personal data or our privacy policy, please contact us.

To see all the information we have about you, and to correct any inaccuracies, please write to us at: 

Paul Fraser Collectibles

2nd Floor

Dean House

94 Whiteladies Road

Bristol

BS8 2QX

UK

**How to unsubscribe**  

If you no longer wish to receive any further email messages, post or other communications from us or you no longer wish to be contacted by other companies who you permitted us to provide your details to then please contact us or change your account settings accordingly. 

**Changes to privacy policy**  

We reserve the right to change our privacy policy, whilst of course keeping it within all relevant legislation and guidelines. We will do all we can to ensure that these pages show the most up to date information at all times, and may notify you of such changes by uploading the revised privacy policy on the Paul Fraser Collectibles website.
